https://yippy.com/privacy-policy-tos.php

The right  search. Unrivaled privacy.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Commitment
Yippy, Inc. ("Yippy or We ") is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of the users of our services. The following describes the information collection and use practices for the services offered on Yippy.com ("Yippy") and other properties.
Data Collection (Absence of Personally Identifiable Information)
No personally identifiable information is ever required by Yippy. This means Yippy never seeks any information related to your name, telephone number, address, or even your email address unless you request a Yippy Service where that information is required. Yippy is intended to be an anonymous service. We do collect limited non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available, which is not saved after session ends. This log information may include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referral data, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies (described below) that may uniquely identify your browser while in a session. Yippy will not track anyone for any reason, unless such information is required to comply with court orders or subpoenas or when required to do so by law, which as of 2019 has never occurred in our 10 year history.
Yippy protects your privacy, and always has since inception.
Cookies
We do not use cookies to uniquely identify you or to track your behavior. A “cookie” is a packet of information sent by a server to a Web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses that server, or to cache user preferences (such as but not limited to user selected graphics). We only use cookies to store personalized settings (such as but not limited to display options and adult filter) and to optimize the speed of Yippy for search by caching your results in a session. By default most browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies; and still be able to make searches on Yippy.
Use of Collected Information
Yippy does not sell or provide personally identifiable information to any third parties. Yippy provides no advertising in our search, or third party tracking scripts.
Links
The privacy policy of sites displayed as search results, or otherwise linked to by Yippy, is not controlled by Yippy. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.
Policy Changes
Yippy constantly strives to provide the best service. As new products and changes to existing products are made, Yippy reserves the right to amend this Yippy Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the current information collection and usage practices associated with your use of Yippy. Your use of Yippy is also governed by the Terms of Service.
More Information
If you have any comments or questions about your privacy, please contact info@yippyinc.com
Copyright and Trademark
All contents of this Web site are: Copyright © 2020 Yippy, Inc. All rights reserved.
The Yippy and associated Marks that appear throughout Yippy belong to Yippy, Inc. and are protected by trademark laws. To seek permission to use any of the Yippy Marks, please contact us at info@yippyinc.com
Terms of Service
Welcome! By using or accessing any of the Yippy Inc. services, including, without limitation, the Yippy Inc. sites, such as yippy.com, all domains and through the Yippy Cloud including the EASE (Enterprise application services environment), web browser, content management system, email and search (collectively but not limited to the foregoing, "Yippy Services"), you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions ("Terms of Service").
Content Linked by Yippy
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Yippy Services are developed in some cases by people or entities over which Yippy exercises no control.
Personal Use Only
The Yippy Services are made available for your personal, non-commercial use only. You may not use the Yippy Services to sell a product or service, or to increase traffic to your Web site for commercial reasons, such as advertising sales. You may not take the results from a Yippy search and reformat and display them, or mirror the Yippy home page or results pages on your Web site. You may not "meta-search" Yippy. You may not send automated queries of any sort to the Yippy Services. This prohibition includes, without limitation, a prohibition against: (i) using any software which sends queries to the Yippy Services or any Yippy sites to determine how a website or webpage "ranks" for various queries; (ii) meta-searching; and (iii) performing "offline" searches on any Yippy web site You may not use the Yippy Services in a manner or for a purpose that is prohibited by applicable law. If you want to make commercial use of the Yippy Services, you must enter into an agreement with Yippy to do so in advance. Please contact us for more information at info@yippyinc.com.
Termination
You agree that Yippy may, under certain circumstances and without prior notice, immediately terminate your account and access to the Yippy Services. Cause for such termination shall include, but not be limited to,
Breaches or violations of the Terms of Service or other incorporated agreements or guidelines,
Requests by law enforcement or other government agencies,
A request by you (self-initiated account deletions),
Discontinuance or material modification to the Yippy Services or any part thereof,
Unexpected technical or security issues or problems,
Extended periods of inactivity,
Engagement by you in fraudulent or illegal activities, and/or
Nonpayment of any fees owed by you in connection with the Yippy Services.
Engaging in inappropriate behavior or displaying content that would be objectionable to children.
Termination of your Yippy account includes (i) removal of access to all offerings within the Service, (ii) deletion of your password and all related information, files and content associated with or inside your account or any part thereof, and (iii) barring of further use of the Service. You agree that any termination for cause shall be made in Yippy's sole discretion and that Yippy shall not be liable to you or any third party for any termination of your account or access to the Yippy Services.
Changes in Terms and Conditions
We may modify or terminate our Yippy Services from time to time, for any reason, and without notice, including the right to terminate with or without notice, without liability to you, any other user or any third party. We reserve the right to modify these Terms of Service from time to time without notice. Please review these Terms of Service from time to time so that you will be apprised of any changes.
Disclaimer of Warranties
Yippy disclaims any and all responsibility or liability for the accuracy, content, completeness, legality, reliability, or operability or availability of information or material displayed in the Yippy Services results. Yippy disclaims any responsibility for the deletion, failure to store, mis-delivery, or untimely delivery of any information or material. Yippy disclaims any responsibility for any harm resulting from downloading or accessing any information or material on the Internet through the Yippy Services.
THE YIPPY SERVICES, AND ALL MATERIALS, INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS," WITH NO WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER. YIPPY AND ITS LICENSORS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED, AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS.
YIPPY AND ITS LICENSORS DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES REGARDING THE SECURITY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE YIPPY SERVICES. YIPPY AND ITS LICENSORS DISCLAIM, ANY WARRANTIES FOR ANY INFORMATION OR ADVICE OBTAINED THROUGH THE YIPPY SERVICES. YIPPY AND ITS LICENSORS DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES FOR SERVICES OR GOODS RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED ON THE YIPPY SERVICES OR RECEIVED THROUGH ANY LINKS PROVIDED BY THE YIPPY SERVICES, AS WELL AS FOR ANY INFORMATION OR ADVICE RECEIVED THROUGH ANY LINKS PROVIDED IN THE YIPPY SERVICES.
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE DOWNLOADING OR OTHERWISE OBTAINING MATERIAL OR DATA THROUGH THE USE OF THE YIPPY SERVICES AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR ANY LOSS OF DATA THAT MAY RESULT FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF SUCH MATERIAL OR DATA.
SOME STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE AND JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.
Limitation of Liability
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL YIPPY OR ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY CLAIM RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR THE SUBJECT MATTER HEREOF. SUCH LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO PREVENT RECOVERY OF DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, AND PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHETHER SUCH CLAIM IS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE, (EVEN IF YIPPY OR ITS LICENSORS HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES).
SUCH LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE FROM USE OR MISUSE OF AND RELIANCE ON THE YIPPY SERVICES, FROM INABILITY TO USE THE YIPPY SERVICES, OR FROM THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION, OR TERMINATION OF THE YIPPY SERVICES (INCLUDING SUCH DAMAGES INCURRED BY THIRD PARTIES).
THIS LIMITATION SHALL APPLY WITH RESPECT TO DAMAGES INCURRED BY REASON OF OTHER SERVICES OR GOODS RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED ON THE YIPPY SERVICES OR RECEIVED THROUGH ANY LINKS PROVIDED IN THE YIPPY SERVICES, AS WELL AS BY REASON OF ANY INFORMATION OR ADVICE RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED ON THE YIPPY SERVICES OR RECEIVED THROUGH ANY LINKS PROVIDED IN THE YIPPY SERVICES.
THIS LIMITATION SHALL APPLY, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TO THE COSTS OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, LOST PROFITS, OR LOST DATA. SUCH LIMITATION SHALL FURTHER APPLY WITH RESPECT TO THE PERFORMANCE OR NON-PERFORMANCE OF THE YIPPY SERVICES OR ANY INFORMATION OR MERCHANDISE THAT APPEARS ON, OR IS LINKED OR RELATED IN ANY WAY TO, THE YIPPY SERVICES.
SUCH LIMITATION SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
SOME STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Request for Removal of Links or Cached Materials
Yippy occasionally receives requests from people to remove links from its indices. Because Yippy searches and groups results in subcategories or clouds from third party sources, you will need to contact the originating source (be it Google, Bing, Yahoo or others) with such requests.
General
These Terms of Service will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida, without giving effect to its conflict of laws and/or provisions of your actual state or country of residence. These Terms represent the entire understanding relating to the use of the Yippy Services and shall prevail over any prior or contemporaneous, conflicting or additional communications. If any provision of these Terms of Service is found to be invalid by any court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining Terms of Service, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of these Terms of Service shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision of these Terms of Service. Please contact Yippy corporate headquarters with any questions regarding these Terms of Service.
Trademarks
Yippy and the Yippy logo and other Yippy product names, service names, slogans or logos referenced in these Terms of Service are trademarks or registered trademarks of Yippy, Inc. in the United States and other countries. All other company, product, or service names referenced or mentioned in Terms of Service are used for identification purposes only and are the property of their respective owners.
Copyright and Trademark
All contents of this Web site are: Copyright © 2020 Yippy, Inc. All rights reserved.
About UsInvestor RelationsPrivacy Policy / Terms of Use
© by Yippy Inc. Yippy is a Trademark of Yippy Inc.
